4sgm.com 2010-03-06

# Wholesale PrivacyPolicy

4sgm.com is owned and operated by Four Seasons General Merchandise. We wholeheartedly respect and understand privacy concerns that may arise, so we have created a comprehensive statement summary for you, our loyal customer. Our privacy policy is intended to offer an explanation on how we collect, handle, share and how you yourself may access the data you have provided us.   
If you have any questions, or want further details about this policy, please contact us

  * By e-mail at:  [iss@4sgm.com](mailto:iss@4sgm.com)
  * By phone at: Toll Free **1-877-446-4746 Ext. 704** or directly/internationally at **(323) 826-1199** our business hours are 8am-5pm M-F (PST)
  * By mail at:  Four Seasons General Merchandise 2801 East Vernon Ave. Los Angeles, CA 90058. Please make sure to include your contact information. 

**_To Whom this Statement Applies_**  
Please read this privacy policy because some might extend to you (the customer) outside and beyond the use of this website.

**_What Information Do We Collect?_**   
We collect various types of information depending on your use of our site. 

**When you become a 4sgm.com registered user** **  
** We initially ask for your e-mail, password, first name, phone number and zip/postal code (to calculate shipping), this is also referred to as “Express Registration”. During full registration we ask additional details such as: time availability, reseller number, and optional information that includes product category interest, business type, number of employees, store size, franchise details, and annual sales. This information is gathered to enhance your shopping experience at 4sgm.com. We also ask for additional information in the section called “business data” with detailed questions and category interests strictly to help us offer services and promotions that may be of interest to you. However, we will uphold your decision if you decline to answer. 

**When you order from us** **  
** We collect your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number (including expiration date and security code) and coupon number [if any]. We will also retain a record of your purchases. For easy reference all of this information will automatically be saved and will be viewable when you login and select the “My Account” page. 

Maintaining security of your personal information is a high priority to us, so we have taken numerous steps to ensure that it is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. The 4sgm.com Web site uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. 

**When you submit website ideas and/or feedback** **  
** We welcome all comments sent regarding our website. Any written submissions (feedback, suggestions, ideas, confidential, original work of any kind) sent to 4sgm.com shall exclusively remain as property of 4sgm.com. Four Seasons General Merchandise will not reveal any information you disclose but we hold the right to use the data for our own analysis. Your identity will remain anonymous.

**When you refer our product(s) to your friends** **  
** We will simply need your e-mail address (for authenticity and confirmation) as well as your friend’s e-mail address and name. However, if that friend views the product(s) but does not register, they will never hear from us again.

> __Refer to a Friend__   
>  Four Seasons General Merchandise has made it easier to share with your friends and business partners the treasures found on 4sgm.com. Now with the click of a button you can do that! Plus there is also a field to put a private message! It is important for you to know that 4sgm.com does not sensor or filter inappropriate language or behavior. Four Seasons General Merchandise holds no responsibility for the contents that are written and transmitted through the Refer to a Friend feature.

**When you leave a product rating/comment** **  
** You have the option to leave behind your own personal comment for each product. This will serve as invaluable input on many levels such as marketing and buying. 

**When you apply for a credit line** **  
** You will be asked to provide your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and other reference information needed to verify your identity, such as your business details. This information is required to process your application.  [Learn more about the 4sgm.com credit program here](http://www.4sgm.com/is-bin/INTERSHOP.enfinity/WFS/4sgm-Storefront-Site/en_US/-/USD/ViewStatic-Start;pgid=9JykiKCIRUBSR0ooqkPIgafi0000kOML1_oO?WorkingTemplate=static%2FOpenCreditAccount)

**We may acquire customer lists from other parties** **  
** So that we may invite new people to visit 4sgm.com. Our policy is to acquire lists of people who have indicated that they are willing to receive e-mail offers. Also, each time we send an e-mail offer, we provide people with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future e-mail offers. 

**_How Do We Use Your Information?_**  
We may or may not use your information in the following ways: 

**To serve you better  
**We might combine the information you provide to us online, in our showroom and through our catalogs. We do not, however, update the information ourselves; each customer is responsible for changing information accordingly. We will use that information to personalize our services, which include (but is not limited to) providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think may be of interest to you.

**To improve the content on our web site  
**For example, we may use cookies to find out which parts of our site or our products are visited most often and improve the content of that particular section.

**To enhance your online shopping experience**  
For example, we may use it to recognize you and welcome you to the site. 

**For marketing and promotional purposes** **  
** For example, we send out e-mail and direct mail to our customers about products or events that we think may be of interest to them. We also may send you offer for discounts or free services (e.g., free shipping).  

**_Do We Share Your Information?_**  
4sgm.com respects your privacy. We do not sell, rent, loan, or transfer any personal information regarding our customers to any unrelated third parties. All the information that is gathered is used for internal marketing purposes that cater to your business needs! 

**_Can I Access My Information?_**  
If you are a registered user of 4sgm.com, you can access and even update your information (including billing and shipping preferences) under the My Account section.

**_

Is It Secure to Shop on 4sgm.com?

_**  
Yes. 4sgm.com uses Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") for secure transmissions. SSL applies encryption to provide confidentiality between two communicating applications, such as your PC and our Internet server. Encryption is defined as a process for scrambling data to prevent illicit entry into a system or interception of information as it travels over the network. That's why you must use an SSL enabled browser to access 4sgm.com. When your data is transmitted over the Internet, it is encrypted at the sending end and then decrypted at the receiving end. 

4sgm.com also carries the [BBBOnLine Reliability seal](http://www.bbbonline.org/cks.asp?id=1060403155446), to provide our customers with assurance that they will have a reliable online shopping experience. 

**_What Are Cookies and Do We Use Them?_**  
**A cookie** is a small piece of information sent by a Web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to interact with you and personalize your experience. At 4sgm.com, we use session cookies.

Session cookies exist only for as long as your browser remains open. Meaning, once you close your browser window the cookies (and all its information) disappear. We use session cookies to maintain information we need to have in order for you to shop at 4sgm.com. For example, the Session ID cookie that we ask your browser to record might be the ID for your order. Without the Session ID cookie, you cannot add merchandise to your shopping order and carry it to Checkout. Cookies can be used by a web site to recognize you. But that does not necessarily mean any personal information is stored in the cookies. At 4sgm.com, we store no personal information about you in the cookies. Anything you choose to tell us about yourself (such as your address and e-mail address) is stored safely and separately on our servers. You will be prompted to provide a password to access this information every time.

**_Your California Privacy Rights_**  
Four Seasons General Merchandise gathers and collects various types of personal information about customers and prospects both online and offline. California residents are granted allowance to request what and to whom your personal information is being disclosed. However, Four Seasons General Merchandise does not disclose any information to anybody. The information gathered is strictly and solely used internally for marketing purposes to improve your overall 4sgm.com experience. You will receive customized information only if you customized your details. If you would like a full report please send an e-mail to [iss@4sgm.com](mailto:iss@4sgm.com) or call (323) 826-1199 for more information.  
**_

How Often Does This Policy Change?

_**  
Please remember that Four Seasons General Merchandise continually strives to improve our services, issues and need for change that comes with the Internet. This privacy policy will likely be edited without notice, for that reason we strongly advise that you check back to this policy frequently.
